(PEOPLE VOCALIZING
RHYTHMICALLY)
(MORE VOICES JOIN IN
VOCALIZATION)
(FOOTSTEPS)
ALL:  ♪ Born of cold
and winter air
♪ And mountain rain combining
♪ This icy force
both foul and fair
♪ Has a frozen heart
worth mining
♪ So cut through the heart
♪ Cold and clear
♪ Strike for love
and strike for fear
♪ See the beauty
sharp and sheer
♪ Split the ice apart
♪ And break the frozen heart
Hup, ho
♪ Watch your step
Let it go
♪ Hup, ho
♪ Watch your step
Let it go
♪ Beautiful
♪ Powerful
♪ Dangerous
♪ Cold
♪ Ice has a magic
Can't be controlled
♪ Stronger than one
♪ Stronger than ten
♪ Stronger than a hundred men!
(ALL GRUNT)
(GRUNTS) Oh!
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Born of cold
And winter air
♪ And mountain rain combining
♪ This icy force
both foul and fair
♪ Has a frozen heart
worth mining
♪ Cut through the heart
♪ Cold and clear
♪ Strike for love
and strike for fear
♪ There's beauty
and there's danger here
♪ Split the ice apart
♪ Beware the frozen heart ♪
(GRUNTS)
KRISTOFF: Come on, Sven.
Elsa. Psst!
Elsa! (GRUNTS)
Wake up. Wake up.
Wake up!
Anna, go back to sleep.
(SIGHS) I just can't.
The sky is awake,
so I'm awake.
So, we have to play.
Go play by yourself.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Do you want to build
a snowman?
Come on, come on,
come on!
(SHUSHING)
(BOTH GIGGLING)
ANNA: Do the magic!
Do the magic!
Oh...
Ready?
Uh-huh. (CHUCKLES)
This is amazing!
(ANNA SCREAMING EXCITEDLY)
Watch this!
(GIGGLING)
Hi, I'm Olaf,
and I like warm hugs.
I love you, Olaf!
(GIGGLES)
ANNA: Olaf...
(GIGGLING)
Tickle bumps!
Oh!
Hang on!
Catch me!
Gotcha!
Again!
Wait!
Whoo-hoo!
Slow down!
(GRUNTS)
Whoo!
Anna!
(GRUNTS)
(ELSA GASPS)
Anna!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Mama! Papa!
(SOBBING) No, no...
You're okay, Anna.
I got you.
(GASPS) Elsa,
what have you done?
This is getting
out of hand.
It was an accident.
I'm sorry, Anna!
Oh. She's ice cold.
I know where we have to go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Ice?
Faster, Sven. (PANTING)
(WHISPERS) Sven!
(SVEN PANTING)
Please! Help!
It's my daughter.
(GASPS)
It's the king.
(ALL MURMURING)
Trolls? (GASPS)
Shush!
I'm trying to listen.
Cuties. I'm going to keep you.
Your Majesty.
Born with the powers,
or cursed?
(STAMMERING) Born.
And they're getting stronger.
Here, here.
You are lucky
it wasn't her heart.
The heart is not
so easily changed.
But the head can
be persuaded.
Do what you must.
I recommend
we remove all magic.
Even memories of magic,
to be safe.
But don't worry.
I'll leave the fun.
(SIGHS)
She will be okay.
But she won't remember
I have powers?
It's for the best.
Listen to me, Elsa.
Your power will only grow.
There is beauty in it...
(TROLLS GASPING)
But also great danger.
(GASPS)
You must learn
to control it.
Fear will be your enemy.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
KING: No!
We'll protect her.
She can learn to control it.
I'm sure.
Until then...
We'll lock the gates.
We'll reduce the staff.
We will limit her contact
with people,
and keep her powers
hidden from everyone.
Including Anna.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ah. (GIGGLING)
Elsa?
(KNOCKS RHYTHMICALLY)
♪ Do you wanna build
a snowman?
♪ Come on, let's go and play
♪ I never see you anymore
♪ Come out the door
♪ It's like you've gone away
♪ We used to be best buddies
And now we're not
♪ I wish you would tell me why
♪ Do you wanna build
a snowman?
(MUFFLED)  ♪ It doesn't
have to be a snowman
ELSA: Go away, Anna.
♪ Okay, bye ♪
(GASPS)
KING: The gloves will help.
See? Conceal it.
Don't feel it.
BOTH: Don't let it show.
(GIGGLES)
♪ Do you wanna
build a snowman?
♪ Or ride our bike
around the halls?
(CLATTERS)
♪ I think some company
is overdue
♪ I've started talking
To the pictures on the walls
Hang in there, Joan.
♪ It gets a little lonely
All these empty rooms
♪ Just watching
the hours tick by ♪
(MIMICKING TICKING)
I'm scared.
It's getting stronger!
Getting upset only makes
it worse. Calm down.
No! Don't touch me!
Please,
I don't want to hurt you.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
See you in two weeks!
Do you have to go?
You'll be fine, Elsa.
Your Highness.
Elsa?
♪ Please
I know you're in there
♪ People are asking
where you've been
♪ They say "Have courage"
And I'm trying to
♪ I'm right out here for you
♪ Just let me in
♪ We only have each other
It's just you and me
♪ What are we gonna do?
♪ Do you wanna build
a snowman? ♪
(SOBBING)
CAPTAIN: All ashore!
Welcome to Arendelle!
(MAN THANKING IN FRENCH)
Watch your step, please.
The gates will be
opening soon.
Why do I have
to wear this?
Because the queen
has come of age.
It's Coronation Day!
That's not my fault.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(CHUCKLES) What do
you want, Sven?
"Give me a snack."
What's the magic word?
"Please."
Uh! Uh-uh-uh. Share.
I can't believe they're
finally opening up the gates!
And for a whole day!
(GIGGLES) Faster, Percy!
(SIGHS) Arendelle, our most
mysterious trade partner.
Open those gates
so I may unlock
your secrets
and exploit your riches.
Did I say that out loud?
Oh! Me sore eyes
can't wait
to see the queen
and the princess.
I bet they are
absolutely lovely.
I bet they are beautiful.
(SNORING)
KAI: Princess Anna?
Princess Anna?
Huh? (CLEARS THROAT) Yeah?
Oh. Sorry to
wake you, ma'am.
No, no, no, you didn't.
(YAWNS)
I've been up for hours.
(SNORING)
(GASPS) Who is it?
(STAMMERS) Still me, ma'am.
The gates will open soon.
Time to get ready.
Of course. (CLEARS THROAT)
Ready for what?
Your sister's coronation,
ma'am.
My sister's corneration.
(GASPS) It's Coronation Day!
(CHUCKLES)
It's Coronation Day!
(EXCLAIMS)
♪ The window is open!
♪ So's that door!
♪ I didn't know
they did that anymore
♪ Who knew we owned
8,000 salad plates?
♪ For years I've roamed
these empty halls
♪ Why have a ballroom
with no balls?
♪ Finally
They're opening up the gates!
♪ There'll be actual,
real, live people
♪ It'll be totally strange
♪ But wow!
Am I so ready for this change!
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ There'll be music
♪ There'll be light
♪ For the first time
♪ In forever
♪ I'll be dancing
through the night
♪ Don't know
if I'm elated or gassy
♪ But I'm somewhere
in that zone
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ I won't be alone
I can't wait to meet everyone!
(GASPS)
What if I meet The One?
(CHEEPS)
♪ Tonight
Imagine me gown and all
♪ Fetchingly draped
against the wall
♪ The picture
of sophisticated grace
♪ I suddenly see him
standing there
♪ A beautiful stranger
♪ Tall and fair
♪ I wanna stuff
some chocolate in my face!
♪ But then we laugh
and talk all evening
♪ Which is totally bizarre
♪ Nothing like the life
I've led so far
♪ For the first time
in forever
♪ There'll be magic
There'll be fun
♪ For the first time
in forever
♪ I could be noticed
by someone
♪ And I know
it is totally crazy
♪ To dream I'd find romance
♪ But for the first time
in forever
♪ At least
I've got a chance! ♪
(INHALES)
♪ Don't let them in
♪ Don't let them see
♪ Be the good girl
♪ You always have to be
♪ Conceal
♪ Don't feel
♪ Put on a show
♪ Make one wrong move
♪ And everyone will know
♪ But it's only for today
♪ It's only for today
♪ It's agony to wait
♪ Tell the guards to open up
♪ The gate
ANNA:  ♪ The gate
♪ For the first time
in forever
♪ Don't let them in
Don't let them see
♪ I'm getting
what I'm dreaming of
♪ Be the good girl
♪ You always have to be
♪ A chance to change
♪ My lonely world
ELSA:  ♪ Conceal
♪ A chance to find true love
♪ Conceal, don't feel
Don't let them know
♪ I know it all ends tomorrow
♪ So it has to be today!
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ For the first time
♪ In forever
♪ Nothing's in my way! ♪
(EXCLAIMING)
(YELPS)
Hey!
I'm so sorry.
Are you hurt?
Hey. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Uh... (STUTTERS)
No, no, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I just wasn't
looking where I was going.
But I'm great, actually.
Oh... Thank goodness.
Oh! Uh...
Prince Hans
of the Southern Isles.
Princess Anna of Arendelle.
"Princess"? My Lady.
Oh!
(SNORTS)
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
(CHUCKLES) Um...
Whew.
Hi. Again.
(BOTH YELP)
Oh, boy!
This is awkward.
Not "You're awkward,"
but just because we're...
I'm awkward, you're gorgeous.
Wait, what?
I'd like to
formally apologize
for hitting the princess
of Arendelle with my horse.
And for every moment after.
No! No, no. It's fine.
I'm not that princess.
I mean, if you
had hit my sister Elsa,
it would be... Yeesh!
(CHUCKLES)
Because, you know...
Hello.
(NEIGHS)
But, lucky you,
it's just me.
(CHUCKLES)
"Just" you?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(BELLS CHIMING)
(SIGHS)
The bells. The coronation.
(STUTTERS) I better go.
I have to go.
I better go. Uh...
Bye!
(BOARDS CREAKING)
Oh, no. Oh!
(SPLASHING)
(SPUTTERS)
(ALL VOCALIZING IN HARMONY)
(MAN SNORING)
(BISHOP CLEARS THROAT)
Your Majesty,
the gloves.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(CHANTING PRAYER)
(GASPS)
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
ALL: Queen Elsa of Arendelle!
(ALL CHEERING)
(PLAYING LIVELY MUSIC)
(GUESTS LAUGHING AND CHATTING)
(MUSIC CEASES)
(APPLAUSE)
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
Princess Anna of Arendelle.
(PANTING)
(GIGGLES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh. Here? Are you sure?
Because I don't think
I'm supposed to...
Oh. Okay.
(ANNA CLEARS THROAT)
Hi.
"Hi" me? Oh...
Um... Hi.
You look beautiful.
Thank you. (CHUCKLES)
You look beautiful-ler.
I mean, not "fuller."
You don't look fuller.
But more beautiful.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you.
So...
This is what a party
looks like.
It's warmer than I thought.
What is that amazing smell?
(BOTH SNIFFING)
BOTH: Chocolate. (CHUCKLING)
KAI: Your Majesty.
The Duke of Weaseltown.
"Weselton"!
Duke of Weselton,
Your Majesty.
As your closest partner in
trade it seems only fitting
that I offer you
your first dance as queen.
One-two, and jump.
(GASPS)
(BOTH SNICKERING)
(CLEARS THROAT) Uh...
Thank you.
Only, I don't dance.
Oh...
But my sister does.
(CHUCKLES)
What?
Oh! Lucky you.
Oh, I don't think...
DUKE: If you swoon,
let me know. I'll catch you.
Sorry.
Like an agile peacock.
(WARBLING)
Ow! Ow.
Speaking of, so great
to have the gates open.
Why did they shut them
in the first place?
Do you know
the reason? Hmm?
No.
All right. Hang on!
(GASPS)
They don't call me
the "Little Dipper"
for nothing!
Oh-ho!
Like a chicken with the face
of a monkey, I fly.
WOMAN: Your Majesty.
DUKE: Let me know
when you're ready
for another round, Milady.
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES) Well,
he was sprightly.
(GROANS) Especially
for a man in heels.
Are you okay?
(CHUCKLES)
I've never been better.
This is so nice.
I wish it could be
like this all the time.
Me, too.
But it can't.
Why not?
It just can't.
(SIGHS)
Excuse me for a minute.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SNIFFLING)
MAN: I'd be honored.
(EXCLAIMING)
(GASPS)
Glad I caught you.
Hans.
(CHUCKLES)
Oop.
(SOFT ORCHESTRAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
I often had a whole parlor
to myself to slide!
Oh!
Oops!
Sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
Your physique helps,
I'm sure, too.
(CHUCKLES)
Ah.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
What's this?
Uh, I was born with it.
Although, I dreamed
I was kissed by a troll.
I like it.
Yeah, the whole thing.
(CHUCKLES)
You got it.
Okay, wait, wait.
So, you have
how many brothers?
Twelve older brothers.
Three of them
pretended I was invisible,
literally, for two years.
That's horrible.
It's what brothers do.
And sisters.
Elsa and I were really close
when we were little.
But then, one day,
she just shut me out,
and I never knew why.
I would never
shut you out.
(GASPS)
Okay, can I just say
something crazy?
I love crazy.
♪ All my life has been
A series of doors in my face
♪ And then suddenly
I bump into you
I was thinking the same thing,
because, like...
♪ I've been searching
my whole life
♪ To find my own place
♪ And maybe
it's the party talking
♪ Or the chocolate fondue
(CHUCKLES)
♪ But with you
I found my place
♪ I see your face
BOTH:  ♪ And it's nothing like
I've ever known before
♪ Love is an open
♪ Door!
♪ Door
BOTH:  ♪ Love is an open door
♪ With you
(BOTH SNICKER)
(EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
♪ I mean, it's crazy
What?
♪ We finish each other's
♪ Sandwiches
That's what I was gonna say!
♪ I've never met someone
BOTH:  ♪ Who thinks
so much like me
Jinx! Jinx again!
♪ Our mental synchronization
Can have but one explanation
♪ You
♪ And I
♪ Were
♪ Just
BOTH:  ♪ Meant to be
♪ Say goodbye
BOTH:  ♪ To the pain
of the past
♪ We don't have
to feel it anymore
♪ Love is an open door
♪ Love is an open
♪ Door
BOTH:  ♪ Life can be
so much more
♪ With you
BOTH:  ♪ Love is an open
♪ Door
♪ Door ♪
Can I say something crazy?
(GIGGLES)
Will you marry me?
(GASPS)
Can I say something
even crazier?
Yes!
ANNA: Coming through.
HANS: Excuse me. Oh...
ANNA: Pardon. Sorry.
WOMAN: Oh!
Can we just get
around you there?
Thank you.
Oh! There she is.
Elsa!
I mean, Queen.
Me again. Um...
May I present Prince Hans
of the Southern Isles.
Your Majesty.
BOTH: We would like...
Uh, your blessing...
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
BOTH: Of our marriage.
Marriage?
Yes! (SQUEALS)
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Well, we haven't worked out
all the details ourselves.
We'll need a few days
to plan the ceremony.
Of course, we'll have soup,
roast and ice cream.
And then... (GASPS)
Wait. Would we live here?
Here?
Absolutely!
Anna!
Oh!
We can invite all 12 of your
brothers to stay with us.
What? No, no, no.
Of course we have the room.
Wait, slow down.
No one's brothers
are staying here.
No one is getting married.
Wait, what?
May I talk to you, please?
Alone.
No. Whatever you have to say,
you can say to both of us.
Fine. You can't marry
a man you just met.
You can if it's true love.
Anna, what do you know
about true love?
More than you.
All you know is how
to shut people out.
(GASPS)
You asked for my blessing,
but my answer is no.
Now, excuse me.
Your Majesty,
if I may ease your...
No, you may not. (STUTTERS)
And I think you should go.
The party is over.
Close the gates.
KAI: Yes, Your Majesty.
What?
Elsa, no, no! Wait.
(GASPS)
Give me my glove!
Elsa, please, please.
I can't live
like this anymore!
Then leave.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
What did I ever do to you?
Enough, Anna.
No, why?
Why do you shut me out?
Why do you shut the world out?
What are you so afraid of?
I said, enough!
(GUESTS SHRIEKING)
(GUESTS MUTTERING NERVOUSLY)
Sorcery.
I knew there was something
dubious going on here.
Elsa.
(SIGHS)
WOMAN: There she is!
(ALL CHEERING)
(ELSA BREATHING HEAVILY)
MAN 1: Yes! It is her!
Queen Elsa.
MAN 2: Our beautiful queen!
Your Majesty?
Are you all right?
No.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL GASP IN AWE)
There she is! Stop her!
Please, just stay away
from me. Stay away.
(ALL SCREAMING)
Monster. Monster!
(BABY CRYING)
(SHUDDERS)
(ALL MURMURING FEARFULLY)
Elsa!
(PANTING)
ANNA: Elsa!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Wait, please!
Elsa, stop!
Anna!
No.
The fjord.
Snow!
Snow?
Yes, snow.
Are you all right?
No.
Did you know?
Look, it's snowing.
It's snowing!
The queen has
cursed this land!
She must be stopped!
You have to go after her.
Wait, no!
You! Is there sorcery
in you, too?
Are you a monster, too?
No, no.
I'm completely ordinary.
That's right, she is.
In the best way.
And my sister
is not a monster.
She nearly killed me!
You slipped on ice.
Her ice.
It was an accident.
She was scared.
She didn't mean it.
She didn't mean any of this.
Tonight was my fault.
I pushed her.
So, I'm the one
that needs
to go after her.
What?
Bring me
my horse, please.
Anna, no.
It's too dangerous.
(SCOFFS) Elsa is
not dangerous.
I'll bring her back,
and I'll make this right.
I'm coming with you.
No, I need you here
to take care of Arendelle.
On my honor.
(GRUNTS)
I leave Prince Hans
in charge.
(ALL MURMURING)
Are you sure
you can trust her?
I don't want you
getting hurt.
She's my sister.
She would never hurt me.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(CROWD MUTTERING)
♪ The snow glows white
On the mountain tonight
♪ Not a footprint to be seen
♪ A kingdom of isolation
♪ And it looks like
I'm the queen
♪ The wind is howling
♪ Like this
swirling storm inside
♪ Couldn't keep it in
Heaven knows I tried
♪ Don't let them in
Don't let them see
♪ Be the good girl
You always have to be
♪ Conceal, don't feel
Don't let them know
♪ Well, now they know
♪ Let it go!
Let it go!
♪ Can't hold it back anymore
♪ Let it go!
Let it go!
♪ Turn away and slam the door
♪ I don't care
♪ What they're going to say
♪ Let the storm rage on
♪ The cold never
bothered me anyway
♪ It's funny how some distance
Makes everything seem small
♪ And the fears
that once controlled me
♪ Can't get to me at all
♪ It's time to see
what I can do
♪ To test the limits
and break through
♪ No right, no wrong
♪ No rules for me
♪ I'm free!
♪ Let it go!
♪ I am one with
the wind and sky
♪ Let it go!
Let it go!
♪ You'll never see me cry
♪ Here I stand
♪ And here I'll stay
♪ Let the storm rage on
♪ My power flurries
through the air
♪ Into the ground
♪ My soul is spiraling
in frozen fractals
♪ All around
♪ And one thought crystallizes
Like an icy blast
♪ I'm never going back
♪ The past is in the past
♪ Let it go!
Let it go!
♪ And I'll rise
like the break of dawn
♪ Let it go!
Let it go!
♪ That perfect girl is gone
♪ Here I stand
♪ In the light of day
♪ Let the storm rage on!
♪ The cold never
bothered me anyway ♪
ANNA: Elsa!
Elsa!
Elsa, it's me, Anna,
your sister who didn't mean
to make you freeze the summer.
I'm sorry.
(SHIVERING) It's all my fault.
Of course, none of it
would have happened
if she had just told
me her secret.
(CHUCKLES) She's a stinker.
(GASPS) Whoa!
(SPUTTERS)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
Oh, no. No, no, no!
Come back!
No, no, no!
(SHIVERING) Okay.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
Snow. It had to be snow.
She couldn't have
had tropical magic
that covered the fjords
in white sand and warm...
Fire! (CHUCKLES)
(SHRIEKING)
(GRUNTS)
(SHIVERING)
Cold, cold, cold,
cold, cold.
(CONTINUES SHIVERING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(READING)
Ooh. "And sauna"!
(GASPS)
(WIND HOWLING)
(SHIVERS)
Yoo-hoo.
Hmm?
Big summer blowout.
Half off
swimming suits, clogs,
and a sun balm
of my own invention, yah?
Oh. Great. For now, um,
how about boots?
Winter boots and dresses?
That would be
in our winter department.
Oh. Um...
I was just wondering.
Has another young woman...
The queen perhaps,
I don't know,
passed through here?
The only one crazy enough
to be out in this storm
is you, dear.
(DOOR OPENS)
(PANTING)
You and this fellow.
Yoo-hoo.
Big summer blowout.
(ANNA HUMMING NONCHALANTLY)
KRISTOFF: Carrots.
Huh?
Behind you.
Oh! Right. Excuse me.
Oh. A real
howler in July, yes?
Wherever could it be
coming from?
KRISTOFF: The North Mountain.
North Mountain.
That will be 40.
Forty? No, 10.
Oh, dear, that's no good.
See, this is from
our winter stock,
where supply and demand
have a big problem.
You want to talk about
a supply and demand problem?
I sell ice for a living.
Ooh. That's a rough business
to be in right now.
(CHUCKLES) I mean,
that is really...
(CLEARS THROAT) That's
unfortunate.
Still 40.
But I will throw in
a visit to Oaken's sauna.
Yoo-hoo. Hi, family.
ALL: Yoo-hoo!
Ten is all I got.
Help me out.
Okay. Ten will get you
this and no more.
Okay, just tell me
one thing.
What was happening
on the North Mountain?
Did it seem magical?
(EXHALES) Yes!
Now, back up while I deal
with this crook, here.
(GULPS)
What did you call me?
KRISTOFF: Okay, okay.
I'm out.
Whoa! (GRUNTS)
Bye-bye.
(SPUTTERS)
No, Sven,
I didn't get your carrots.
(GROANS)
But I did find us
a place to sleep.
And it's free.
(SNORTS)
I'm sorry about
this violence.
I will add
a quart of lutefisk,
so we have good feelings.
Just the outfit
and the boots, yah?
Uh...
(TUNE BEING PICKED ON LUTE)
♪ Reindeers are better
than people
♪ Sven,
don't you think that's true?
♪ "Yeah, people will beat you
And curse you and cheat you
♪ "Every one of them's bad,
except you"
Aw. Thanks, buddy.
♪ But people smell
better than reindeers
♪ Sven,
don't you think I'm right?
♪ "That's once again true
For all, except you"
♪ You got me
Let's call it a night
♪ "Good night"
♪ Don't let the frostbite
♪ Bite ♪
Nice duet.
(GASPS)
(SIGHS) It's just you.
What do you want?
I want you to take me up
the North Mountain.
I don't take people places.
Let me rephrase that.
(GROANS) Hey.
Take me up
the North Mountain.
Please.
(SNIFFING)
Look, I know how
to stop this winter.
(SIGHS)
We leave at dawn.
And you forgot
the carrots for Sven.
(GRUNTS)
Oops, sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't... (CLEARS THROAT)
We leave now.
Right now.
Whew!
(URGING SVEN)
(ANNA SHRIEKS)
(ANNA CHUCKLES BREATHLESSLY)
Hang on!
We like to go fast.
I like fast.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa...
Get your feet down.
This is fresh lacquer.
Seriously,
were you raised in a barn?
(SPITS)
Ugh!
No, I was raised
in a castle.
Hmm.
KRISTOFF: So, uh, tell me,
what made the queen go
all ice-crazy?
Oh. Well...
It was all my fault.
I got engaged,
but then she freaked out,
because I'd only just
met him, you know, that day.
And she said she wouldn't
bless the marriage, and...
Wait. You got engaged
to someone you
just met that day?
Yeah. Anyway, I got mad,
and so she got mad,
and then she tried
to walk away,
and I grabbed her glove...
Hang on!
You mean to tell me
you got engaged
to someone you just
met that day?
Yes. Pay attention.
But the thing is, she wore
the gloves all the time
so, I just thought, maybe she
has a thing about dirt.
Didn't your parents ever
warn you about strangers?
Yes, they did.
But Hans is not a stranger.
Oh, yeah?
What's his last name?
(SCOFFS) "Of the
Southern Isles."
What's his favorite food?
Sandwiches.
Best friend's name?
Probably John.
Eye color?
Dreamy.
Foot size?
Foot size doesn't matter.
Have you had a meal
with him yet?
What if you hate
the way he eats?
the way he picks his nose?
Picks his nose?
And eats it.
Excuse me, sir.
He is a prince.
All men do it.
Ew.
Look, it doesn't matter.
It's true love.
It doesn't sound
like true love.
(SCOFFS) Are you some
sort of love expert?
No. But, uh, I have
friends who are.
You have friends
who are love experts?
I'm not buying it.
Stop talking.
No, no, no. No, no.
I'd like to meet these...
No, I mean it.
(GRUNTS)
(SHUSHES)
(LOW GROWLING)
Sven, go.
Go!
What are they?
Wolves.
Wolves?
What do we do?
I got this.
You just... Don't fall off,
and don't get eaten.
But I want to help!
No.
Why not?
Because I don't
trust your judgment.
Excuse me?
Who marries a man
she just met?
It's true love!
Whoa!
(GRUNTS)
Whoa. Whoa!
Christopher!
It's "Kristoff"!
Ow! (YELPS)
(KRISTOFF GRUNTING)
Duck!
(SCREAMS)
(SNARLING)
You almost set me on fire!
But I didn't.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SVEN GROANS)
(BOTH GASP)
Get ready to jump, Sven!
You don't tell him what to do.
Hey!
I do!
Jump, Sven!
(GRUNTS)
(KRISTOFF YELLING)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
Phew!
(WHIMPERS)
But I just paid it off.
Uh-oh. No. No.
No!
Ah! No, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
ANNA: Grab on!
Pull, Sven. Pull!
(KRISTOFF GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(SLED THUDS)
Whoa.
(KRISTOFF GROANS)
I'll replace your sled,
and everything in it.
And I understand
if you don't want
to help me anymore.
(GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
Of course I don't want to help
her anymore. In fact,
this whole thing has
ruined me for helping
anyone ever again.
ANNA: It's this way?
"She'll die on her own."
I can live with that.
ANNA: Here we go.
"But you won't get
your new sled if she's dead."
ANNA: I think, actually,
it's up.
Sometimes,
I really don't like you.
(PANTING)
Hold up! We're coming.
You are?
I mean, sure.
I'll let you tag along.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(ANNA GASPS)
Arendelle.
It's completely frozen.
(SIGHS)
But it will be fine.
Elsa will thaw it.
Will she?
Yeah. Now, come on.
This way
to the North Mountain?
(CHUCKLES)
More like this way.
(GASPS)
(ICE TINKLING)
(GRUNTING EXCITEDLY)
I never knew winter
could be so beautiful.
OLAF: Yeah.
It really is beautiful,
isn't it?
But it's so white.
You know,
how about a little color?
I'm thinking maybe some
crimson, chartreuse.
How about yellow?
No, not yellow.
Yellow and snow?
(SHUDDERS) No go.
(CHUCKLES)
(BOTH GASP)
Am I right?
(SHRIEKS)
Hi.
You're creepy.
OLAF: Whoa!
I don't want it.
Back at you.
OLAF: Please don't drop me.
No.
Come on,
it's just a head.
OLAF: All right.
We got off to a bad start.
Ew, ew, ew, the body!
(GROANS)
Wait, what am I looking
at right now?
Why are you hanging off
the earth like a bat?
All right, wait one second.
Oh. Uh...
Oh!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now, I'm perfect.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, almost.
It was like my whole life
got turned upside down.
(GRUNTS)
Oh! Too hard. I'm sorry!
Head rush!
I was just...
Are you okay?
Are you kidding me?
I am wonderful!
I've always wanted a nose.
(IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE)
So cute.
It's like a little
baby unicorn.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
But... Hey! Whoa!
(GASPS)
Oh.
I love it even more.
(EXHALES) All right,
let's start this thing over.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Olaf.
And I like warm hugs.
Olaf?
That's right. Olaf.
And you are?
Oh. Um...
I'm Anna.
And who's the funky-looking
donkey over there?
That's Sven.
Uh-huh.
And who's the reindeer?
Sven.
Oh, the... Oh. Okay.
That makes things
easier for me.
(SQUEALS) Aw, look at him
trying to kiss my nose.
I like you, too.
Olaf.
Did Elsa build you?
Yeah. Why?
Do you know
where she is?
Fascinating.
Yeah. Why?
Do you think you could
show us the way?
Yeah. Why?
How does this work? Ow!
Stop it, Sven.
I'm trying to focus, here.
Yeah. Why?
I'll tell you why.
We need Elsa
to bring back summer.
Summer?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh. I don't know why,
but I've always loved
the idea of summer.
And sun,
and all things hot.
Really?
I'm guessing you
don't have much
experience with heat.
Nope.
But sometimes
I like to close my eyes,
and imagine what it would be
like when summer does come.
(SIGHING CONTENTEDLY)
♪ Bees will buzz
Kids will blow dandelion fuzz
♪ And I'll be doing
Whatever snow does in summer
♪ A drink in my hand
♪ My snow up
against the burning sand
♪ Probably getting
gorgeously tanned
♪ In summer
♪ I'll finally see
a summer breeze
♪ Blow away a winter storm
♪ And find out
what happens to solid water
♪ When it gets warm
♪ And I can't wait to see
♪ What my buddies
all think of me
♪ Just imagine
how much cooler I'll be
♪ In summer!
(VOCALIZING)
♪ The hot and the cold
are both so intense
♪ Put them together
It just makes sense
(SCATTING)
♪ Winter's a good time
To stay in and cuddle
♪ But put me in summer
and I'll be a...
♪ Happy snowman!
♪ When life gets rough
♪ I like to hold
on to my dream
♪ Relaxing in the summer sun
Just letting off steam
♪ Oh, the sky
♪ Will be blue
♪ And you guys
will be there, too
♪ When I finally do
♪ What frozen things do
In summer!
I'm gonna tell him.
Don't you dare.
♪ In summer! ♪
So, come on!
Elsa's this way.
Let's go bring back summer!
I'm coming!
(OLAF LAUGHING)
Somebody's gotta
tell him.
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
No, no. You've got
the bark facing down.
The bark needs
to be face-up.
Bark down is drier.
MAN 1: Bark up!
MAN 2: Bark down!
BOY: Papa!
Cloak? Does anyone
need a cloak?
Arendelle is indebted
to you, Your Highness.
The castle is open.
There is soup and hot glogg
in the great hall.
Here, pass these out.
Prince Hans!
Are we expected
to just sit here and freeze
while you give away all
of Arendelle's tradable goods?
Princess Anna
has given her orders.
And that's another thing!
Has it dawned on you
that your princess
may be conspiring
with a wicked sorceress
to destroy us all?
Do not question
the princess.
She left me in charge
and I will not hesitate
to protect Arendelle
from treason.
(STAMMERING) Treason?
(HORSE WHINNYING)
(ALL GASP)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(PEOPLE PANICKING)
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa, boy. Easy.
Easy.
MAN: It's Princess Anna's
horse.
WOMAN 1: So, where is
the princess?
WOMAN 2: Where could she be?
WOMAN 3: Where is she?
Princess Anna is in trouble.
I need volunteers to go
with me to find her.
I'll go.
I volunteer.
I volunteer
two men, My Lord.
Be prepared for anything.
And should you encounter
the queen,
you are to put an end
to this winter.
Do you understand?
Hmm.
So, how exactly
are you planning
to stop this weather?
Oh. I am gonna
talk to my sister.
That's your plan?
My ice business is riding on
you talking to your sister?
Yep.
(GRUNTS)
So, you're not at all
afraid of her?
Why would I be?
Yeah.
I bet she's the nicest,
gentlest, warmest person ever.
Oh. Look at that.
I've been impaled.
(CHUCKLING)
What now?
KRISTOFF: Mmm...
It's too steep.
I've only got one rope
and you don't know
how to climb mountains.
ANNA: Says who?
(GRUNTS)
Hmm?
What are you doing?
I'm going to see my sister.
You're gonna
kill yourself.
(GRUNTS)
I wouldn't put
my foot there.
You're distracting me.
Or there.
How do you know
Elsa even wants to see you?
ANNA: All right.
I'm just blocking you out
because I gotta
concentrate, here. (GRUNTING)
You know,
most people who disappear
into the mountains
want to be alone.
Nobody wants to be alone.
Except maybe you.
I'm not alone.
I have friends, remember?
ANNA: You mean,
the love experts?
Yes, the love experts.
(GRUNTS) Ah...
Please tell me
I'm almost there.
Does the air seem a bit thin
to you up here?
(ANNA PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
Hang on.
OLAF: Hey, Sven?
Not sure if this is gonna
solve the problem
but I found a staircase
that leads exactly
where you wanted to go.
Ha-ha! Thank goodness.
Catch!
(BOTH GRUNT)
Thanks. That was like
a crazy trust exercise.
(OLAF CHUCKLING)
BOTH: Whoa.
Now, that's ice.
I might cry.
Go ahead.
I won't judge.
(GRUNTS)
All right, take it easy,
boy. Come here.
I got you. (GRUNTS)
Okay. You stay
right here, buddy.
(WHISTLES)
Flawless.
Knock.
Just knock.
Why isn't
she knocking?
Do you think
she knows how to knock?
(GASPS)
(EXHALES) Huh.
It opened.
That's a first.
Oh. You should probably
wait out here.
What?
The last time
I introduced her to a guy,
she froze everything.
But, but...
Oh, come on!
It's a palace made of ice.
Ice is my life!
Bye, Sven.
You, too, Olaf.
Me?
Just give us a minute.
Okay.
(SOFTLY) One, two,
three...
BOTH: Four...
Whoa.
Elsa?
It's me, Anna.
(EXCLAIMS)
ELSA: Anna.
(GASPS)
Whoa. Elsa,
you look different.
It's a good different.
And this place...
It's amazing.
Thank you.
I never knew
what I was capable of.
I'm so sorry
about what happened.
If I'd have known...
No, no, no. It's okay.
You don't have
to apologize, but you
should probably go.
Please.
But I just got here.
You belong down
in Arendelle.
So do you.
No, Anna,
I belong here.
Alone.
Where I can be who I am
without hurting anybody.
Actually, about that...
OLAF: Sixty!
Wait. What is that?
Hi! I'm Olaf
and I like warm hugs!
Olaf?
Yeah. You built me.
Remember that?
And you're alive?
(STAMMERS) Um...
I think so.
He's just like the one
we built as kids.
Yeah.
Elsa, we were so close.
We can be like
that again.
YOUNG ANNA:  Catch me!
YOUNG ELSA:  Slow down!
(GRUNTS)
Anna!
(GASPS) No.
We can't. Goodbye, Anna.
Elsa, wait.
No, I'm just trying
to protect you.
You don't have to protect me.
I'm not afraid.
Please don't
shut me out again.
♪ Please don't slam the door
♪ You don't have to keep
Your distance anymore
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ I finally understand
♪ For the first time
in forever
♪ We can fix this hand in hand
We can head down
this mountain together.
♪ You don't have
to live in fear
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ I will be right here
Anna.
♪ Please go back home
♪ Your life awaits
♪ Go enjoy the sun
And open up the gates
Yeah, but...
I know.
♪ You mean well
But leave me be
♪ Yes, I'm alone
♪ But I'm alone and free
♪ Just stay away
And you'll be safe from me
♪ Actually, we're not
♪ What do you mean,
you're not?
♪ I get the feeling
you don't know
♪ What do I not know?
♪ Arendelle's in deep,
deep, deep
♪ Deep snow ♪
What?
You kind of set off
an eternal winter everywhere.
Everywhere?
Well, it's okay,
you can just unfreeze it.
No, I can't.
I don't know how.
Sure you can.
I know you can.
♪ 'Cause for the first time
in forever
♪ Oh, I'm such a fool!
I can't be free!
♪ You don't have to be afraid
♪ No escape from
the storm inside of me
♪ We can work
this out together
♪ I can't control the curse!
♪ We'll reverse the storm
you've made
♪ Anna, please you'll
only make it worse!
♪ Don't panic
♪ There's so much fear!
♪ We'll make
the sun shine bright
♪ You're not safe here!
♪ We can face
this thing together
♪ No!
♪ We can change
this winter weather
♪ And everything
will be all right
♪ I can't! ♪
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
KRISTOFF: Anna!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Who's this?
Wait, it doesn't matter.
Just...
You have to go.
No, I know we can
figure this out together.
How?
What power do you have
to stop this winter?
To stop me?
Anna, I think we should go.
No, I'm not leaving
without you, Elsa.
Yes, you are.
(LOW GROWLING)
(GASPS)
(GROWLS)
ANNA: Stop! Put us down!
Go away.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SHUDDERING)
(BOTH YELP)
Heads up!
Watch out for my butt!
(BOTH GASP)
It is not nice
to throw people!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
feisty-pants. Okay, relax.
Just calm down! Calm down!
Okay! All right!
I'm okay.
Just let the snowman be.
I'm calm.
Great.
(GRUNTS)
Oh! Come on!
(ROARING)
Oh. Look, see?
Now, you made him mad.
I'll distract him.
You guys go.
No, no! Not you guys!
(MUFFLED) This just got
a whole lot harder.
(ANNA SHRIEKS)
(GROWLS)
KRISTOFF: Look out!
(ANNA SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
(ANNA GASPS)
(BOTH PANTING)
KRISTOFF: Run! Run!
KRISTOFF: What are you doing?
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
I got him! (LAUGHS)
KRISTOFF: Whoa! Stop!
ANNA: It's a 100-foot drop.
KRISTOFF: It's 200.
Ow!
What's that for?
I'm digging a snow anchor.
Okay. What if we fall?
There's 20 feet of fresh
powder down there.
It'll be like landing
on a pillow.
Hopefully.
(GASPS)
(ROARING)
Okay, Anna. On three.
ANNA: Okay.
KRISTOFF: One...
You tell me when.
I'm ready to go.
Two...
I was born ready! Yes!
Calm down.
(GRUNTS)
ANNA: Tree!
What the... Whoa!
(BOTH GRUNT)
KRISTOFF: That happened.
(PANTING) Man,
am I out of shape.
(GASPS)
There we go. Hey, Anna!
Sven! Where did
you guys go?
We totally lost
Marshmallow back there.
Hey! We were just
talking about you.
All good things,
all good things.
No!
(GRUNTING)
This is not making much
of a difference, is it?
(SHRIEKS)
Olaf!
(GRUNTS) Hang in there, guys!
Go. Go faster!
(BOTH STRUGGLING)
Wait, what?
KRISTOFF: Hey!
(MARSHMALLOW GROWLING)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Ow!
Kristoff!
(ANNA GASPING)
Don't come back!
We won't.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
Hey, you were right.
Just like a pillow. (CHUCKLES)
(OLAF PANTING)
Olaf!
I can't feel my legs!
(COUGHING)
Those are my legs.
Ooh!
Hey, do me a favor,
grab my butt.
Oh. That feels better.
Hey, Sven! He found us.
Who's my cute
little reindeer?
Don't talk to him like that.
(CHUCKLING)
You're tickling me.
Here.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Thank you.
How's your head?
Ah! Ooh!
(STAMMERING)
It's fine. Uh...
Uh, I'm good.
I've got a thick skull.
I don't have a skull.
Or bones.
So, uh...
So, now what?
Now what? (CHUCKLES)
Now what?
Oh...
What am I gonna do?
She threw me out.
I can't go back to Arendelle
with the weather like this.
And then there's
your ice business.
Hey, hey. Don't worry
about my ice business.
Worry about your hair!
What? I just fell off a cliff.
You should see your hair.
No, yours is
turning white.
White? It's...
What?
It's because she struck you,
isn't it?
Does it look bad?
No.
You hesitated.
No, I didn't.
Anna, you need help, okay?
Come on.
Okay! Where are we going?
To see my friends.
The love experts?
Love experts?
Uh-huh.
And don't worry,
they'll be able to fix this.
How do you know?
Because I've seen them
do it before.
I like to consider myself
a love expert.
(SVEN GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Get it together.
Control it.
Don't feel. Don't feel.
Don't feel.
Don't feel! (GASPS)
(ICE CRACKLING)
Look, Sven, the sky is awake.
(SHIVERING)
Are you cold?
A little.
(CLEARS THROAT) Uh...
Wait. Come here.
Huh?
Ooh. (SIGHS)
So, uh, about my friends.
Well... (CHUCKLES)
I say "friends"...
They're more like family.
Anyway, when I was a kid,
it was just me and Sven.
Until they, you know,
kinda took us in.
They did?
Yeah.
I don't want to scare you.
They can be a little
inappropriate and loud.
(CHUCKLES) Very loud.
They are also stubborn
at times,
and a little overbearing.
And heavy.
Really, really, heavy.
(STAMMERS) But you'll get it.
They mean well.
Kristoff,
they sound wonderful.
Okay, then.
(OLAF GRUNTS)
Meet my family.
Hey, guys.
They're rocks.
KRISTOFF: You are
a sight for sore eyes.
(WHISPERS) He's crazy.
Rocko's looking sharp,
as usual.
Clay, whoa...
I don't even recognize you.
You lost so much weight.
(WHISPERS) I'll distract
him while you run.
(IN LOUD VOICE)
Hi, Sven's family!
It's nice to meet you.
(WHISPERS) Because I love you,
Anna, I insist you run.
(IN LOUD VOICE) I understand
you're love experts. Ooh!
(WHISPERS) Why aren't
you running?
Uh...
Okay. Well, I'm gonna go.
OLAF: Go.
No, no, no. Anna, wait.
(GASPS)
Kristoff! (GASPING)
KRISTOFF: Whoa! (CHUCKLING)
Hey!
Kristoff's home!
(ALL CLAMORING EXCITEDLY)
TROLL 1: Kristoff's here!
Kristoff's home!
Wait, "Kristoff"?
Uh-huh.
Ah, let me look at you.
Take off your clothes,
I wash them.
No! No, I'm going
to keep my clothes on.
Look, it's great
to see you all,
but where's Granpabbie?
TROLL KID: He's napping.
But look, I grew a mushroom.
I...
I earned my fire crystal.
I passed a kidney stone.
Kristoff, pick me up.
(GRUNTS) You're getting big.
Good for you.
Trolls. They're trolls!
He's brought a girl!
ALL: (CHEERING) A girl!
Whoa!
TROLL 2: Is that
a real girl?
TROLL 3: She's like
a little cupcake.
What's going on?
I've learned
to just roll with it.
Let me see.
Bright eyes, working nose,
strong teeth!
(CHUCKLES)
Yes, yes. She'll do
nicely for our Kristoff.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, um, no.
No. (CHUCKLES)
You've got the wrong idea.
No. That's not why
I brought her here.
Right. We're not... I'm not...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
What's the issue, dear?
Why are you holding back
from such a man?
♪ Is it the clumpy way
he walks?
What?
♪ Or the grumpy way he talks?
Oh, no.
♪ Or the pear-shaped,
square-shaped
♪ Weirdness of his feet?
KRISTOFF: Hey!
♪ And though we know
he washes well
♪ He always ends up
sort of smelly
♪ But you'll never
meet a fella
BOTH:  ♪ Who's as
sensitive and sweet
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
That's nice, but...
BOTH:  ♪ So, he's a bit
of a fixer-upper
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
♪ So, he's got a few flaws
TROLL 1:  ♪ Like his
peculiar brain, dear
TROLL 2:  ♪ His thing
with the reindeer
BOTH:  ♪ That's a little
outside of nature's laws
This is not about me!
♪ So, he's a bit
of a fixer-upper
♪ But this we're certain of
♪ You can fix
this fixer-upper up
♪ With a little bit of love
Um...
Can we please
just stop talking
about this?
We've got a real,
actual problem, here.
I'll say.
So, tell me, dear...
♪ Is it the way
that he runs scared?
♪ Or that he's
socially impaired?
♪ Or that he only likes
To tinkle in the woods?
I don't need to know that.
♪ Are you holding back
your fondness
♪ Due to his
unmanly blondness?
(CHUCKLES)
♪ Or the way he covers up
That he's the honest goods?
♪ He's just a bit
of a fixer-upper
♪ He's got a couple of bugs
No, I don't!
♪ His isolation
is confirmation
♪ Of his desperation
for healing hugs
Aw.
♪ So, he's a bit
of fixer-upper
♪ But we know what to do
♪ The way to fix up
this fixer-upper
♪ Is to fix him up with you
BOTH: Whoa!
Stop it, stop it,
stop it! Enough!
She is engaged
to someone else, okay?
♪ So, she's a bit
of fixer-upper
♪ That's a minor thing
♪ Her quote "engagement"
Is a flex arrangement
♪ And by the way,
I don't see no ring
♪ So, she's a bit
of a fixer-upper
Hey! Whoa, watch it!
♪ Her brain's a bit betwixt
♪ Get the fiance
out of the way
♪ And the whole thing
will be fixed
(GROANS)
(ALL VOCALIZING)
♪ We're not saying
you can change him
♪ 'Cause people
don't really change
♪ We're only saying
that love's a force
♪ That's powerful and strange
♪ People make bad choices
♪ If they're mad
or scared or stressed
♪ But throw
a little love their way
♪ Throw a little love
their way
♪ And you'll bring
out their best
♪ True love brings
out the best
♪ Everyone's a bit
of a fixer-upper
♪ That's what it's all about
Father!
Sister!
Brother!
♪ We need each other
to raise us up
♪ And round us out
♪ Everyone's a bit
of a fixer-upper
♪ But when push comes to shove
♪ The only fixer-upper fixer
♪ That can fix
a fixer-upper is...
♪ True, true
♪ True
♪ Love!
♪ Love, love, love
♪ Love
True love
♪ True
Do you, Anna,
take Kristoff to be
your trollfully wedded...
Wait, what?
You're getting married.
♪ Love! ♪
(HYPERVENTILATING)
Anna?
She's as cold as ice.
There is strange magic here.
Granpabbie.
Come, come.
Bring her here to me.
Anna, your life is
in danger.
There is ice in your heart
put there by your sister.
If not removed,
to solid ice will
you freeze, forever.
What? No.
But you can
remove it, right?
I cannot.
I'm sorry, Kristoff.
If it was her head,
that would be easy.
But only an act of true love
can thaw a frozen heart.
An act of true love?
A true love's kiss,
perhaps?
(GASPING)
TROLL 1: Something's wrong.
TROLL 2: Are you all right?
Anna, we've got to get
you back to Hans.
Hans.
Pull us out, Sven.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Olaf, come on!
I'm coming!
(TROLL KIDS GIGGLING)
Let's go kiss Hans!
Who is this Hans?
(SOLDIERS TALKING
INDISTINCTLY)
We are here to find
Princess Anna.
Be on guard,
but no harm is
to come to the queen.
Do you understand?
SOLDIER 1: Yes, Your Grace.
(SOLDIERS AGREEING)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(ROARS)
The queen.
(GRUNTS)
DUKE'S THUG 2: Go, go!
Come on!
(GASPING)
DUKE'S THUG 2: There!
DUKE'S THUG 1: Up there!
Come on!
DUKE'S THUG 2: We got her.
No. Please.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
DUKE'S THUG 2: Go around.
Toss it.
Stay away!
DUKE'S THUG 1: Look out!
DUKE'S THUG 2: Fire! Fire!
Get her!
(MARSHMALLOW GROWLS)
Ah!
(YELLS)
Come on!
(ROARING)
(GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
SOLDIER: Grab his arm.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
DUKE'S THUG 2: Aim...
(WHIMPERS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
SOLDIER 1: This way, this way!
SOLDIER 2: Whoa!
Queen Elsa!
Don't be the monster
they fear you are.
(PANTING)
(ICE TINKLING)
(GASPS)
(YELLING)
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
Oh, no. What have...
What have I done?
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(GASPS)
Why did you
bring me here?
I couldn't just
let them kill you.
But I'm a danger
to Arendelle. Get Anna.
Anna has not returned.
(GASPS)
If you would just
stop the winter.
Bring back summer, please.
Don't you see?
I can't.
(SIGHS)
You have to tell them
to let me go.
I will do what I can.
(DOOR LOCKS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIMPERING)
(KRISTOFF PANTING)
(ANNA EXHALES SHARPLY)
Just hang in there.
Come on, buddy, faster!
(VOCALIZING)
Oh, boy!
Whoa! I'll meet you guys
at the castle!
KRISTOFF: Stay out
of sight, Olaf.
OLAF: I will!
Hello!
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
It's alive!
It's Princess Anna!
(KRISTOFF PANTING)
(ANNA SHIVERING)
(GROANS)
(SHIVERING) Are you
gonna be okay?
Don't worry about me.
(DOOR OPENS)
WOMAN: Anna!
You had us worried sick.
My Lady.
Get her warm. And find
Prince Hans, immediately.
We will. Thank you.
Make sure she's safe.
WOMAN: Oh, you poor girl,
you're freezing.
Oh, let's get you inside now
and get you warm.
(WHIMPERS)
(SVEN WHINING)
I'm going back out
to look for Princess Anna.
You cannot risk going
out there again.
If anything happens to her...
If anything happens
to the princess,
you are all
Arendelle has left.
(SIGHS)
KAI: He's in here.
Prince Hans.
Anna.
You're so cold.
Hans, you have
to kiss me.
What?
Now! Now!
Slow down.
We'll give you two
some privacy.
What happened out there?
Elsa struck me
with her powers.
You said she would
never hurt you.
I was wrong.
(GROANS)
Anna.
(SHIVERING)
She froze my heart,
and only an act
of true love can save me.
A true love's kiss.
Oh, Anna.
If only there was
someone out there
who loved you.
What?
You said you did.
As thirteenth in line
in my own kingdom,
I didn't stand a chance.
I knew I would have
to marry into
the throne somewhere.
What... What are
you talking about?
As heir, Elsa was
preferable, of course.
But no one was getting
anywhere with her.
But you...
Hans!
You were so desperate
for love,
you were willing
to marry me just like that.
I figured
after we married,
I would have to stage
a little accident for Elsa.
Hans! (GASPS)
No. Stop.
But then,
she doomed herself,
and you were dumb enough
to go after her.
Please.
(CHUCKLES)
All that's left now
is to kill Elsa,
and bring back summer.
You're no match for Elsa.
No, you're no
match for Elsa.
I, on the other hand,
am the hero who is
going to save Arendelle
from destruction.
You won't get
away with this.
Oh...
I already have.
(DOOR LOCKS)
(WHIMPERING)
Please, somebody, help.
(SHIVERING CONTINUES)
Please. Please.
(ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
DUKE: It's getting colder
by the minute.
If we don't do something soon,
we'll all freeze to death.
Prince Hans.
Princess Anna is...
Dead.
What?
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
What happened to her?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
She was killed.
By Queen Elsa.
ALL: (GASP) No!
Her own sister.
At least we got to say
our marriage vows
before she died in my arms.
There can be no doubt now.
Queen Elsa is a monster,
and we are all
in grave danger.
Prince Hans,
Arendelle looks to you.
With a heavy heart,
I charge Queen Elsa
of Arendelle with treason.
And sentence her to death.
(SIGHS)
(STRAINING)
GUARD 1: Hurry up!
GUARD 2: She's dangerous.
Move quickly.
GUARD 3: Careful.
(STRAINING)
It won't open!
GUARD 1: It's frozen shut.
GUARD 2: Put your back
into it!
GUARD 4: Come on! Push!
(ALL GRUNT)
(GROWLS)
(WHINES)
(SNORTING)
What is it, buddy?
Hey, watch it.
What's wrong with you?
(GRUNTING)
I don't understand you
when you talk like that.
(YELPS) Stop it!
Put me down!
(SNORTS)
No, Sven!
We're not going back.
(WHINES)
She's with her true love.
(SIGHS)
(WHOOSHING)
What the...
Anna!
(PANTING)
(KRISTOFF GRUNTS)
Come on!
Come on, boy.
(SHIVERING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
(WEAKLY) Help.
(GIGGLING)
(GASPS) Anna!
Oh, no.
(SHRIEKS)
(CONTINUES SHIVERING)
Olaf?
(GASPS)
Olaf. Get away
from there.
Wow!
So, this is heat.
I love it.
Ooh! But don't touch it.
(ANNA GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
So, where's Hans?
What happened to your kiss?
I was wrong about him.
It wasn't true love.
But we ran
all the way here.
Please, Olaf, you can't
stay here. You'll melt.
I am not leaving
here until
we find some other act
of true love to save you.
Do you happen to have
any ideas?
I don't even know
what love is.
That's okay, I do.
Love is
putting someone else's
needs before yours.
Like, you know, how Kristoff
brought you back here
to Hans and left you forever.
(GASPS) Kristoff loves me?
Wow, you really
don't know anything
about love, do you?
Olaf, you're melting.
Some people are
worth melting for.
(MUMBLES)
Just maybe not right
this second.
(YELLS)
Don't worry,
I've got it.
(PANTING)
We're gonna get through...
Oh, wait.
Hang on,
I'm getting something.
(GASPS) It's Kristoff
and Sven!
They're coming back this way.
They... They are?
Wow! He's really
moving fast.
I guess I was wrong.
I guess Kristoff doesn't
love you enough
to leave you behind.
Help me up, Olaf. Please.
No, no, no!
You need to stay
by the fire and keep warm.
I need to get to Kristoff.
Why?
(GASPING) Oh, I know why!
There's your act
of true love right there!
Riding across the fjords
like a valiant,
pungent reindeer king!
Come on!
(BOTH GASP)
OLAF: Look out!
(GROANS)
Oh!
(OLAF PANTING)
(BOTH GASP)
Uh... Back this way.
(YELPS)
We're trapped.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS) Oh...
(SQUEALS)
Whoa! (GIGGLES)
Slide, Anna!
(ANNA BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BOTH SHRIEK)
(OLAF VOCALIZING)
(GROANS)
We made it!
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go!
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on, buddy, faster.
(ANNA GROANING)
Kristoff!
(OLAF PANTING)
Keep going!
Kristoff!
Come on!
(SHIVERING)
(WHIMPERING)
No.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Whoa!
(YELLS) Whoa!
Sven... Sven!
(GRUNTING)
Good boy.
(SHIVERING)
(GASPING)
(WEAKLY) Kristoff.
Kristoff...
Anna...
Anna!
(GASPING)
Elsa! You can't
run from this!
Just take care of my sister.
Your sister?
She returned from the mountain
weak and cold.
She said that
you froze her heart.
No.
I tried to save her,
but it was too late.
Her skin was ice.
Her hair turned white.
Your sister is dead.
Because of you.
No.
(WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
(ALL GASP)
(SHIVERING)
(GASPS)
Kristoff.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Anna!
(SWORD UNSHEATHING)
Elsa?
(GRUNTS)
No!
(EXHALES)
(GASPS) Anna!
Oh. Anna!
No, no!
Please, no.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOBBING)
Anna?
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
Anna?
(SIGHS)
Oh, Elsa.
You sacrificed yourself
for me?
I love you.
(GASPS) "An act of true love
will thaw a frozen heart."
"Love will thaw."
Love. Of course.
Elsa?
Love!
(GASPS)
(PEOPLE MURMURING IN AWE)
I knew you could do it.
Hands down, this is
the best day of my life.
And, quite possibly,
the last.
Oh, Olaf!
Hang on, little guy.
Oh, oh, oh!
(GASPS)
My own personal flurry!
(GIGGLES)
(CHUCKLES)
(HANS GROANS)
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Anna?
But she froze your heart.
The only frozen heart
around here is yours.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(ALL CHEERING)
Wonderful!
(ALL EXCLAIMING IN JOY)
(BOTH SIGH)
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
SAILOR: Setting course, sir.
(GROANS)
I will return this scoundrel
to his country.
We shall see
what his 12 big brothers
think of his behavior.
Arendelle thanks you, milord.
This is unacceptable.
I am a victim of fear.
I've been traumatized.
Ah! My neck hurts.
Is there a doctor that
I could see? (STAMMERS)
And I demand
to see the queen!
Oh. I have a message
from the queen.
"Arendelle will
henceforth and forever
"no longer do business
of any sort with Weaseltown."
"Weselton."
It's Weselton!
SOLDIER: Let's go.
Come on, come on, come on!
(STAMMERING)
Okay, okay, here I come.
(GRUNTS) Pole!
Whoops! Sorry.
Okay, okay.
Here we are. Oh!
(SQUEALS EXCITEDLY)
(GASPS)
ANNA: I owe you a sled.
Are you serious?
Yes!
And it's the latest model.
No, I can't accept this.
You have to. No returns.
No exchanges. Queen's orders.
She's named you the Official
Arendelle Ice Master
and Deliverer.
What? That's not a thing.
Oh, sure it is.
And it even has a cup holder.
Do you like it?
Like it? I love it!
Whoa.
(KRISTOFF CHUCKLES)
I could kiss you!
I could. I mean,
I'd like to. I'd...
(STAMMERS) May I? We me.
I mean, may we?
Wait, what?
We may.
Mmm.
Summer!
(GIGGLING)
(GASPS) Ooh...
Hello. (CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFS)
(EXHALES)
(GASPING)
(SNEEZING)
(GASPS)
(SLURPS)
(SQUEALS)
(WHIMPERS)
(BELLOWS)
(CHUCKLING)
Are you ready?
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL GASP)
KID: Ice!
(ALL MUTTERING EXCITEDLY)
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(APPLAUDING)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
WOMAN: Ooh! Whoo-hoo...
Swing me. (CHUCKLES)
Ooh... (WHIMPERS)
I like the open gates.
We are never
closing them again.
(ANNA GASPS)
Oh, Elsa, they're beautiful,
but you know I don't skate.
Come on!
You can do it!
KRISTOFF: Look out.
Reindeer coming through.
I got it, I got it. I don't
got it, I don't got it.
Hey, guys!
That's it, Olaf.
(OLAF CHUCKLES)
Glide and pivot.
And glide and pivot.
ELSA: Go. (LAUGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LIVELY INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENCHANTING INSTRUMENTAL
(DREAMY INSTRUMENTAL
MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL
(GROANING)
Oh!
(SIGHS)